



91 Lincoln St. apt 5 Cambridge, MA 02141



314-583-3742



wiegand.alex@gmail.com



alex-wiegand.netlify.app

OBJECTIVE

A veteran of the restaurant industry for over 14 years, I have experience working as part of a team in a fast paced, ever-changing environment. I also have practical experience in designing, developing, and launching a product. I am seeking to leverage this experience to enter the tech industry.

I specialize in Web/UI/UX design with JavaScript frameworks such as React and Svelte, as well as developing full stack applications with the PERN stack.

ALEX WIEGAND

EXPERIENCE

Bambara Kitchen and Bar

Lead Bartender • February 2018 – February 2021 Cambridge, MA

Saloon

Bartender • March 2017 – February 2018 Summerville, MA

Park Restaurant and Bar

Bartender • January 2016 – September 2017 Cambridge, MA

Over my career I have created new cocktail menus and respectively trained front of house staff quarterly, as well as trained new bartenders upon hire. I have hosted and arranged pop-up bars and cocktail competitions. At Bambara Kitchen and Bar I helped reduce back stock by nearly 10,000 USD.

EDUCATION

Berklee College of Music Boston, MA

MY TOOLKIT

| * | JavaScript | * | React | * | Svelte | * | Webpack |
|---|------------|---|-------|---|---------|---|---------|
| * | CSS | * | Sass | * | HTML5 | * | Git |
| * | Postgres | * | Bash | * | Express | * | Node |

Proficient in all major operating systems.

MY CERTIFICATES

- **❖** CodeCademy
- The Modern JavaScript Bootcamp Andrew Mead Udemy
- Learn JavaScript Online- Jad Joubran

OTHER ACCOMPLISHMENTS

- Judges Choice Tito's Mary Madness 2019
- ❖ Featured in *Imbibe* magazine October 2019

REFERENCES

Available on request.